[
     {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 1?",
      "correctAnswer": "1",
      "options": [
        "1",
        "3",
        "6",
        "-1"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 19?",
      "correctAnswer": "361",
      "options": [
        "359",
        "363",
        "361",
        "366"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 56?",
      "correctAnswer": "3136",
      "options": [
        "3136",
        "3141",
        "3138",
        "3134"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 57?",
      "correctAnswer": "3249",
      "options": [
        "3251",
        "3247",
        "3249",
        "3254"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 64?",
      "correctAnswer": "4096",
      "options": [
        "4098",
        "4096",
        "4094",
        "4101"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 48?",
      "correctAnswer": "2304",
      "options": [
        "2302",
        "2304",
        "2306",
        "2309"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 38?",
      "correctAnswer": "1444",
      "options": [
        "1442",
        "1446",
        "1444",
        "1449"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 34?",
      "correctAnswer": "1156",
      "options": [
        "1156",
        "1154",
        "1158",
        "1161"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 20?",
      "correctAnswer": "400",
      "options": [
        "398",
        "402",
        "405",
        "400"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 89?",
      "correctAnswer": "7921",
      "options": [
        "7919",
        "7923",
        "7926",
        "7921"
      ]
    }
]